/**
 * @type {{
 *  question: string,
 *  answers: [ string, string ] | [ string, string, string ] | [ string, string, string, string ],
 *  correct: number,
 *  time: number
 * }[] }
 */
export const questions = [
    {
        question: "What was the first micro-computer called?",
        answers: [
            "Apple 8800",
            "Altair 8800",
            "MacOS"
            
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Who co-founded Apple with Steve Jobs?",
        answers: [
            "Larry Page",
            "Xerox",
            "Steve Wozniak",
            "Bill Gates"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What number system is comprised of just 0s and 1s?",
        answers: [
            "Base 10",
            "Base 1",
            "Base 2"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Who created the original verson of MacOS?",
        answers: [
            "Steve Jobs",
            "Larry Page",
            "Bill Gates"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "____ is a free online service that can be used to quicky convert videos, images, or other files to another format. ?",
        answers: [
            "Cloud Convert",
            "McAfee",
            "FileConverterPro"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What is ASCll standard used for?",
        answers: [
            "Normalize the size of RAM and CPU chips across PCs",
            "Allow the computer to run faster",
            "Convert between binary data and human-readable characters"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What was the original meaning of the term Computer?",
        answers: [
            "An old form of a mechanical calculator",
            "A person who did computations professionally",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What is ASCll standard used for?",
        answers: [
            "Normalize the size of RAM and CPU chips across PCs",
            "Allow the computer to run faster",
            "Convert between binary data and human-readable characters"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first thing we covered in this class?",
        answers: [
            "Hardware",
            "Photo editing",
            "Software",
            "The history of the first micro-computer"
        ],
        correct: 3,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "which one is the closing tag?",
        answers: [
            "<p>",
            "</p>"
            
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    }
    
]
